{
    "chapters": [
        {
            "chapter1": [
                {
                    "topic": "topic1",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question1",
                            "answer": "answer1"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question2",
                            "answer": "answer2"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic2",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question3",
                            "answer": "answer3"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question4",
                            "answer": "answer4"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic3",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question5",
                            "answer": "answer5"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question6",
                            "answer": "answer6"
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "chapter2": [
                {
                    "topic": "topic4",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question7",
                            "answer": "answer7"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question8",
                            "answer": "answer8"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic5",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question9",
                            "answer": "answer9"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question10",
                            "answer": "answer10"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic6",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question11",
                            "answer": "answer11"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question12",
                            "answer": "answer12"
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "chapter3": [
                {
                    "topic": "topic7",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question13",
                            "answer": "answer13"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question14",
                            "answer": "answer14"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic8",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question15",
                            "answer": "answer15"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question16",
                            "answer": "answer16"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic9",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question17",
                            "answer": "answer17"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question18",
                            "answer": "answer18"
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "chapter4": [
                {
                    "topic": "topic10",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question19",
                            "answer": "answer19"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question20",
                            "answer": "answer20"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic11",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question21",
                            "answer": "answer21"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question22",
                            "answer": "answer22"
                        }
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "topic": "topic12",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "question": "question23",
                            "answer": "answer23"
                        },
                        {
                            "question": "question24",
                            "answer": "answer24"
                        }
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}